<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Two Activities</string>
    <string name="button_label_one">Text 1</string>
    <string name="button_label_two">Text 2</string>
    <string name="button_label_three">Text 3</string>
    <string name="article_text_one">In a vault deep inside Abbey Road Studios in London — protected by an unmarked, triple-locked, police-alarmed door — are something like 400 hours of unreleased Beatles recordings, starting from June 2, 1962 and ending with the very last tracks recorded for the <i>Let It Be</i> album. The best of the best were released by Apple Records in the form of the 3-volume Anthology series.
        For more information, see the Beatles Time Capsule at www.rockument.com.
\n\n
This volume starts with the first new Beatle song, “Free as a Bird” (based on a John Lennon demo, found only on <i>The Lost Lennon Tapes Vol. 28</i>, and covers the very earliest historical recordings, outtakes from the first albums, and live recordings from early concerts and BBC Radio sessions.
\n\n
<b>Highlights include:</b>
\n\n
<b><i>Cry for a Shadow</i></b> - Many a Beatle fanatic started down the outtake road, like I did, with a first listen to this song. Originally titled “Beatle Bop” and recorded in a single session that yielded four songs (the other three featured Tony Sheridan with the Beatles as a backing band), “Cry for a Shadow” is an instrumental written by Lennon and Harrison, which makes it unique to this day. John Lennon plays rhythm guitar, George Harrison plays lead guitar, Paul McCartney plays bass, and Pete Best plays drums. The sessions were produced by Bert Kaempfert in Hamburg, Germany, during the Beatles’ second visit from April through July of 1961 to play in the Reeperbahn-section clubs.
\n\n
<b><i>My Bonnie</i></b> and <b><i>Ain’t She Sweet</i></b> — At the same session, the Beatles played on “My Bonnie” (the first-ever single with Beatles playing), as the backing band for English singer Tony Sheridan, originally a member of the Jets. The popularity of this single in Liverpool brought the Beatles to the attention of Brian Epstein, who worked in the NEMS record store and tried to meet demand for the disc. John Lennon then sings a fine “Ain’t She Sweet” (his first-ever released vocal).
\n\n
<b><i>Searchin</i></b> — A Jerry Leiber - Mike Stoller comedy song that was a hit for the Coasters in 1957, and a popular live favorite of the Beatles. The Coasters also had a hit with “Besame Mucho” and the Beatles covered that song as well. Ringo Starr had by now replaced Pete Best on drums. The high falsetto is George, who also plays a hesitant lead guitar. This is from their first audition for Decca Records in London on Jan 1., 1962, live in the studio. The Grateful Dead would later cover “Searchin” with a similar arrangement, Pigpen doing the Paul vocals. A live version is available on outtake records featuring the Dead joined by the Beach Boys!
\n\n
<b><i>Love Me Do</i></b> — An early version of the song, played a bit slower and with more of a blues feeling, and a cool bossa-nova beat in middle. Paul had to sing while John played harmonica — a first for the group. Pete Best played drums on this version.
\n\n
<b><i>She Loves You – Till There Was You – Twist and Shout</i></b> — Live at the Princess Wales Theatre by Leicester Square in London, attended by the Queen. “Till There Was You” (by Meredith Wilson) is from the musical The Music Man and a hit for Peggy Lee in 1961. Before playing it, Paul said it was recorded by his favorite American group, “Sophie Tucker” (which got some laughs). At the end, John tells the people in the cheaper seats to clap their hands, and the rest to “rattle your jewelry” and then announces “Twist and Shout” (a song by Bert Russell and Phil Medley that was first recorded in 1962 by the Isley Brothers). A film of the performance shows the Queen smiling at John’s remark.
\n\n
<b><i>Leave My Kitten Alone</i></b> — One of the lost Beatle songs recorded during the “Beatles For Sale” sessions but never released. This song, written by Little Willie John, Titus Turner, and James McDougal, was a 1959 R&amp;B hit for Little Willie John and covered by Johnny Preston before the Beatles tried it and shelved it. A reference to a “big fat bulldog” may have influenced John’s “Hey Bulldog” (Yellow Submarine album), which is a similar rocker.
\n\n
<b><i>One After 909</i></b> — A song recorded for the <i>Let It Be</i> album was actually worked on way back in the beginning, six years earlier. This take shows how they did it much more slowly, with an R&amp;B feel to it.
</string>
    <string name="article_text_two">An estimated 56 percent of dogs in the U.S. are overweight or obese.*
How do you identify a healthy weight goal for your dog if he’s overweight (or underweight)?
\n\n
Most people turn to resources on the internet for an average dog weight or a range. Because all dogs are different, though, it’s not that simple.

Dog breeds can have large weight ranges and they usually vary from male to females, too. If you have a mixed breed, this makes things even more complicated.

Purina developed the Body Condition System (BCS) for veterinarians to help eliminate confusion when it comes to assessing a dog’s weight.
        \n\nAccording to Dr. Callie Harris, DVM, “The BCS is a nine-point scale that can help your veterinarian assess your dog’s body condition and the severity of his weight problem.”

Feeding your dog a healthy weight dog food can help him achieve and maintain his ideal weight.

\n\n

Problems with Identifying an “Average” Dog Weight
Since dogs come in so many different breeds and sizes, it’s impossible to identify an average weight for all dogs. Weight may also depend on the dog’s sex and whether they’ve been spayed or neutered.
\n\n
Although many resources provide an average weight range for different breeds, it’s usually significant. These ranges often don’t take the dog’s sex and other factors into consideration.
\n\n
For example, a typical weight range you might see for a Labrador Retriever is 55 to 80 pounds. That’s a big range, and most female Labs shouldn’t weigh 80 pounds. They should fall on the lower end of the range.
\n\n
Weight ranges also don’t account for the many mixed breed dogs out there. Just because the typical range for a Lab is 55 to 80 pounds doesn’t mean your Lab mix will or should fall within that range. It depends on the other breeds he’s mixed with.

Plus, what if you don’t know the breed makeup of your mixed-breed dog? What then? Most resources say to use the dominant breed, but even then, you’re guessing what that is. An average dog weight or range definitely doesn’t work for mixed breeds.


\n\n
A Better Solution for Determining Healthy Dog Weight
Rather than going off an average, which can be grossly inaccurate, veterinarians use our Body Condition System (BCS). With this system, your veterinarian uses physical and visual observations of your dog to assess his current body condition and whether he’s too heavy or too thin.</string>

    <string name="article_text_three">Cats are far more similar to their wild ancestors than dogs are to wolves, so dogs are in that sense the more domesticated of the two species. As they adapted to living alongside humans, cats became more sociable with one another and much more accepting of people, but there is no evidence that they have changed much more than that over the past few thousand years.
        \n\n  Will cats, which require meat, eventually evolve to eat a broader array of foods as dogs do?
\n\n
Cats and dogs belong to a group of mammals known as Carnivora, and the wild ancestors of both species dined primarily on meat. Recent DNA analyses indicate that over the course of their evolution, dogs have acquired more copies of the so-called amylase gene, which makes an enzyme that helps to break down starch. Having more copies of this gene has allowed dogs to eat a more omnivorous diet. In contrast, the cat family, known as Felidae, lost the genes that encode several key enzymes—including those that manufacture vitamin A, prostaglandins and the amino acid taurine—early in its evolution. Whereas dogs (and humans) can synthesize these substances from plant-based precursors, cats have to obtain them from meat. To expand their diet, cats would have to evolve physiological traits that allow them to synthesize these and other key nutrients from plant foods. This capacity has not emerged during the 10 million years of felid evolution, so it seems unlikely to arise spontaneously in our domestic cats.</string>
</resources>